[{"answer": "I am the wrong person to ask.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Why do you think you've been able to inspire that kind of loyalty?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "The truth.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What do you work on other than making great music, but in terms of your relationship with an audience, what do you work on you think that brings you that extra time?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "As someone who'd always been in the background like you say, the moment you went center stage, did you in that moment realize, wow, OK, this is what it's all about?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, I did.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Did you that night?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "It was like floating.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "But when you got that reaction from the crowd, and that was the first time you'd had it, what was the experience like to you?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, for me, I kind of knock me over.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "What's the answer in your case?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Well, I think that everyone who's not famous assumes it is the greatest thing that could happen.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Wouldn't you think that fame would be the greatest thing to happen to a person, you know?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "And yet the fact that you mentor the acts on \"Idol,\" you've done it a couple of times --", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "-- whoa, how's she handle this, you know?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I would do that every day if I could.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "If you're concerned about what may happen?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I don't think of myself as being famous.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Or is it just a pain in the backside?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, yes, sure.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Have you met anybody in the last 20 years who didn't know who you were?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "But not often, no.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "But not often?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "I just remember them just driving her crazy.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "How much of it has she brought on herself?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Does it worry you that we're going to see more of that with people who just may be off psychologically, a little flawed anyway?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "It's a drug.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "It's a drug, isn't it?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, on that bombshell, we are going to take a quick break so the audience can recover.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "That's what happens, right?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "It's -- just stick to your guns.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What advice would you give that Barry Manilow?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Everybody but the audiences.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Who's they?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, it was dreadful.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "ORGAN: What was that like for you?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Did I say something about our noses?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "You know the concord hooter arrives, you know?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I'm as vain as the next guy.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Are you a vain man, would you say?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "But only with you or with people like you who remind me I'm not the average guy.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Probably more so now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "The average guy isn't earning stratospheric sums of money being a huge headline act in Vegas.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "I say hello to the people out there and that's it, you know?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I had hired a -- my first business manager.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Where did it go?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Since that experience, did you get wiser about money?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Do I know how much I'm worth?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "You know, I thought so.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "That's sad though, isn't it?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "You remember that one?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "So do I.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I mean, I think that it would work again today, don't you?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Oh, I would love it.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "How would you feel ideologically, if McDonald's came to you now and said, would you front a commercial for us?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "But the reason I -- the reason I was dwelling on the sad songs and the heartbreak was that you're quite private bloke, aren't you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Had your heart broken?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes, never.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "I've been in love, but I -- I'm lucky enough never to have my heart broken.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "You've never ever been in love or had your heartbroken?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Shoot, Piers, I don't know.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "How have you avoided what's struck everybody else?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I guess, it's whatever -- I think romance, and love for that sake, is whatever anybody wants it to be.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What's the definition of romance?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "For them, it might be wonderful for them.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "For anybody in the fame game, is it sensible to open your book up like that, do you think?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes, but the old mystique from celebrity -- the star game used to be everyone was on a plinth and you didn't really know much about them.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Am I?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "The best ones that I've come up with are not at the piano, when I'm walking around.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "How do you come up with them?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "You know I didn't write \"Mandy.\"", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "When you do something like \"Mandy,\" where did that come to you?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "\"If I Should Love Again\" was a --", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "\"If I Should Love Again,\" how did you come up with that?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Was she one of the greatest showman you have played with?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "ANILOW: Yeah, Annie Lennox.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "She says is there anyone you have met that really made you feel star struck?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "It is amazing.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I can't imagine myself not --", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Quite interesting, what would you be doing if you hadn't gone into music, do you think?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I would have been playing in some bar at night, complaining about how nobody understands me.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Do you ever wonder?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "I've never heard of that one, I must say.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "\"Let's Hang on.\"", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "That there was one of my songs?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "Well, this one did, yeah.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "When you say wrote in a dream, do you actually mean these things come to you sometimes in dreams?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "This one woke me up.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Do you wake up?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Do you jump out of bed and write it all down?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "The modern crop.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "Who of the modern crop catches your eye?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "Well, I like Sting's work.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 777, "question": "Any other?", "qSentId": 776}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "Do you really think I'm going to tell you that?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "I would never answer that question!", "docId": "110623pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "What is the song that you literally can't hear anymore?", "qSentId": 789}]